<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paulo Breviglieri | Data Science &amp; Machine Learning</title>
    <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://paulobreviglieri.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Paulo Breviglieri | Data Science &amp; Machine Learning</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2020 Paulo Breviglieri | info@paulobreviglieri.com</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://paulobreviglieri.com/media/paulo-breviglieri.svg</url>
      <title>Paulo Breviglieri | Data Science &amp; Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your privacy is of utmost importance. It is Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information that may be collected from you across &lt;a href=&#34;https://paulobreviglieri.com&#34;&gt;paulobreviglieri.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal information may be requested only when truly demanded to provide a service to you. It is collected by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. You will be explicitly notified when and why information from you is collected, and how it will be used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collected information will be retained only for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. Stored data will be protected within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally identifying information will not be shared publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website may link to external sites that are not operated by Paulo Breviglieri. Please be aware that Paulo Breviglieri has no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are free to refuse our occasional request for your personal information, with the understanding that some of your desired services may not be provided to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your continued use of Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s website will be regarded as acceptance of Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how user data and personal information are handled, feel free to contact Paulo Breviglieri.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This policy is effective as of January 1st, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Terms&lt;br/&gt;
By accessing &lt;a href=&#34;https://paulobreviglieri.com&#34;&gt;paulobreviglieri.com&lt;/a&gt;, you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use License&lt;br/&gt;
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s website for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not, unless otherwise stated: modify or copy the materials; use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial); attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s website; remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or transfer the materials to another person or &amp;ldquo;mirror&amp;rdquo; the materials on any other server. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Paulo Breviglieri at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer&lt;br/&gt;
The materials on Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s website are provided on an &amp;lsquo;as is&amp;rsquo; basis. Paulo Breviglieri makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Paulo Breviglieri does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Limitations&lt;br/&gt;
In no event shall Paulo Breviglieri or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s website, even if Paulo Breviglieri or a Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accuracy of materials&lt;br/&gt;
The materials appearing on Paulo Breviglieri&amp;rsquo;s website could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Paulo Breviglieri does not warrant that any of the materials on its website are accurate, complete or current. Paulo Breviglieri may make changes to the materials contained on its website at any time without notice. However, Paulo Breviglieri does not make any commitment to update the materials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Links&lt;br/&gt;
Paulo Breviglieri has not reviewed the sites linked to its website and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Paulo Breviglieri of the site. Use of any such linked website is at the user&amp;rsquo;s own risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modifications&lt;br/&gt;
Paulo Breviglieri may revise these terms of service for its website at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Governing Law&lt;br/&gt;
These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of São Paulo, Brazil and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that State or location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Regressions Enabling Enhanced House Price Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/house-pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/house-pricing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cropland Mapping with Random Forests and Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/cropland-mapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/cropland-mapping/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Pneumonia with Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/detecting-pneumonia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/detecting-pneumonia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/portfolio/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommending Music Artists with Boltzmann Machines</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/recommending-music-artists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/recommending-music-artists/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Grid Stability with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/smart-grid-stability/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/smart-grid-stability/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paulo Breviglieri - Data Science &amp; Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paulobreviglieri.com/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paulobreviglieri.com/home/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
